[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1201_Watcher_Death",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1201_Watcher_Death_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1201_Watcher_Death_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1201_Watcher_Corruption",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1201_Watcher_Corruption_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1201_Watcher_Corruption_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1202_Magistrate_Monarchs",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Magistrate_Monarchs_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1202_Magistrate_Monarchs_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1202_Magistrate_Factions",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Magistrate_Factions_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1202_Magistrate_Factions_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_factionchoiceready",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_factiontalkedto",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1222_Innkeep_WhereNow",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1222_Innkeep_WhereNow_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1222_Innkeep_WhereNow_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1222_Innkeep_WhyHouse",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1222_Innkeep_WhyHouse_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1222_Innkeep_WhyHouse_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Survivalist1203_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@Survivalist1203_01_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@Survivalist1203_01_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1202_Marauder_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Marauder_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1202_Marauder_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_introtomarauders",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1202_Syndicate_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Syndicate_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1202_Syndicate_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_introtosyndicate",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1202_Covenant_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Covenant_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1202_Covenant_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_introtocovenant",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_introtoallfactions_accepted",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1202_Marauder_dye_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Marauder_dye_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1202_Marauder_dye_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_marauderquest1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1202_Syndicate_dye_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Syndicate_dye_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1202_Syndicate_dye_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_syndicatequest1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1202_Covenant_dye_talk",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1202_Covenant_dye_talk_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1202_Covenant_dye_talk_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_covenantquest1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1204_Constable_EncroachingCorruption",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1204_Constable_EncroachingCorruption_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1204_Constable_EncroachingCorruption",
        "AchievementUnlock": "S_encroachingconstable",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1225_Giacomo_HousingGeneral",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingGeneral_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingGeneral_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "S_downpayment",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1225_Giacomo_HousingStorage",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingStorage_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingStorage_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "12_Quest_Housing_3b",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "1225_Giacomo_HousingTrophy",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingTrophy_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@1225_Giacomo_HousingTrophy_Response",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "12_Quest_Housing_6",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
